https://southernlabel.com/privacy-policy/

Capabilities
Apparel Custom Hang TagsPressure Sensitive LabelsCare LabelsAwning Canvas LabelsIron-On LabelsBedding and Furniture Law LabelsCare LabelsPressure Sensitive LabelsUnprinted Tyvek RollsIron-On LabelsThermal Labels/Thermal RibbonsCustom Hang TagsSteri-Fab®Entertainment WristbandsFood & Beverage Pressure Sensitive LabelsThermal Labels/Thermal RibbonsCoupon LabelsStatic Cling LabelsHome & Personal Care Pressure Sensitive LabelsCoupon LabelsThermal Labels/Thermal RibbonsOffice Products WristbandsPrinted/Laminated TyvekPressure Sensitive LabelsThermal Labels/Thermal RibbonsOutdoorRetail Pressure Sensitive LabelsCoupon LabelsStatic Cling LabelsThermal Labels/Thermal RibbonsCustom Hang TagsSeafood Shellfish TagsThermal Labels/Thermal RibbonsPressure Sensitive Labels
Markets
News
FAQ
Contact Us
Download Forms
Why A Privacy Policy?
Southern Label Company respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy (‘Policy’) embodies our commitment to its protection through adherence to fair electronic information practices. This Policy puts you, the individual, in control of how your personal information is processed. You have our promise that we will not electronically process your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this Policy.
This Privacy Policy protects your privacy by informing you about:
The types of personal information Southern Label Company collects about you through its Web Site;
How it collects that information;
The general purposes for which it collects such information;
The choices and means by which individuals may limit its use and disclosure.
Empowering you to choose:
Whether and how certain personal information you provide is used (where such use is unrelated to the uses for which you originally disclosed it); and
Assuring you that Southern Label Company:
Takes reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction
Implements reasonable policies and procedures to ensure that personal information is kept only for the purposes for which it has been gathered
Uses reasonable measures to ensure that we have accurately and completely recorded the personal information you have provided
Provides you reasonable access to your personal information as well as procedures for correcting or modifying that information where appropriate
Ensuring accountability to individuals who believe that Southern Label Company has not complied with these privacy principles.
The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. We also encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.
Our Accountability to You
In addition to the privacy protections that we provide, our employees, agents and business partners are independently responsible for ensuring compliance with this Privacy Policy, as described below. If you feel that Southern Label Company, or any of our agents, representatives or employees, is violating this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at sales@southernlabel.com, by telephone at (205) 836-8080, or by postal mail at: Southern Label Company Attention: WebMaster 5624 Clifford Circle Birmingham, AL 35210 (205) 836-8080
Notification of Changes
We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy 30 days before their effective date so you will always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You are responsible for periodically checking our web site for changes to this Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of any posted change to our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by sending an e-mail to privacy@southernlabel.com If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact privacy@southernlabel.com
